Office of the Registrar, School of Medicine Records UA075
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Student folders, 1961 -- 2005; UA075.002; 141.6 Linear Feet
  - Hartunian, Byron Vartan, 1975; UA075.002.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - Harvey, Frank, 1984; UA075.002.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - Hasenfus, Nancy A., 1981; UA075.002.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - Hatem, David S., 1981; UA075.002.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - Haug, Stephen, 1983; UA075.002.015.00024 (Box 15)
  - Hawkins, Catherine C., 1979; UA075.002.015.00025 (Box 15)
  - Hawronsky, John W., 1984; UA075.002.015.00026 (Box 15)
  - Hayat, Nasser H., 1976; UA075.002.015.00027 (Box 15)
  - Hayden Jr., John David, 1975; UA075.002.015.00028 (Box 15)
  - Hayes, Craig R., 1975; UA075.002.015.00029 (Box 15)
  - Hayes, Edward, 1982; UA075.002.015.00030 (Box 15)
  - Hayes Jr., Francis E., 1978; UA075.002.015.00031 (Box 15)
  - Hayes, Gerard, 1983; UA075.002.015.00032 (Box 15)
  - Hayes, Marie, 1980; UA075.002.015.00033 (Box 15)
  - Hayes, Michael, 1983; UA075.002.015.00034 (Box 15)
  - Haynesworth, Dominic T., 1979; UA075.002.015.00035 (Box 15)
  - Hays, Lewis Simon, 1976; UA075.002.015.00036 (Box 15)
  - Hearon, Bernard Francis, 1977; UA075.002.015.00037 (Box 15)
  - Heck, Christopher C., 1981; UA075.002.015.00038 (Box 15)
  - Hedges III, Thomas R., 1975; UA075.002.015.00039 (Box 15)
  - Heffernan, Robert Edward, 1975; UA075.002.015.00040 (Box 15)
  - Heifetz, Richard W., 1978; UA075.002.015.00041 (Box 15)
  - Heller, James Norman, 1975; UA075.002.015.00042 (Box 15)
  - Helm II, Standiford, 1977; UA075.002.015.00043 (Box 15)
  - Henneberry, Robert Milne, 1966; UA075.002.015.00044 (Box 15)
  - Henning, Kelly J., 1985; UA075.002.015.00045 (Box 15)
  - Hepp, Walter, 1984; UA075.002.015.00046 (Box 15)
  - Herman, Barry, 1980; UA075.002.015.00047 (Box 15)
  - Herman, Richard S., 1977; UA075.002.015.00048 (Box 15)
  - Hernandez, Sandra, 1984; UA075.002.015.00049 (Box 15)
  - Hernandez, William Hector III, 1981; UA075.002.015.00050 (Box 15)
  - Herring, Lynn Berman, 1982; UA075.002.015.00051 (Box 15)
  - Hersh, Layne Marion, 1976; UA075.002.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - Herther, Craig, 1979; UA075.002.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Hewitt, Tomas B.K., 1977; UA075.002.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Higgins, Ilona L, 1974; UA075.002.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Higgins, Michael, 1982; UA075.002.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - Hill, Arthur Charles, 1982; UA075.002.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - Hill Jeffery W., 1977; UA075.002.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Hill, Sophia Paraskos, 1978; UA075.002.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - Hilt, Dana C., 1979; UA075.002.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Hines, Thomas, 1979; UA075.002.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - Hirsch, Sheldon, 1981; UA075.002.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - Ho, Jimmy, 1976; UA075.002.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Ho, Rose Mang Yuen, 1976; UA075.002.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Ho, Samuel Warren, 1976; UA075.002.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - Hocking, Leslie, 1983; UA075.002.016.00015 (Box 16)
  - Hockmuth, Robert, 1982; UA075.002.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Hodge, Mary Beth, 1981; UA075.002.016.00017 (Box 16)
  - Hohler, Charles William II, 1971; UA075.002.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - Holbrook Wick, Shirley, 1979; UA075.002.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - Holstein, Eric, 1984; UA075.002.016.00020 (Box 16)
  - Holyk, Peter R, 1978; UA075.002.016.00021 (Box 16)
  - Holzman, Susan E, 1979; UA075.002.016.00022 (Box 16)
  - Honeychurch, Carol R., 1973; UA075.002.016.00023 (Box 16)
  - Hom, William Lim, 1976; UA075.002.016.00024 (Box 16)
  - Thomas, David Chase, 1976; UA075.002.016.00025 (Box 16)
  - Homer, Stuart M., 1977; UA075.002.016.00026 (Box 16)
  - Horwitz, Tina J, 1979; UA075.002.016.00027 (Box 16)
  - Houle, James P., 1978; UA075.002.016.00028 (Box 16)
  - Hourihan, Mary, 1985; UA075.002.016.00029 (Box 16)
  - Howalt, K. Dane, 1983; UA075.002.016.00030 (Box 16)
  - Howe, Kenneth F., 1981; UA075.002.016.00031 (Box 16)
  - Howell, Clifton, 1983; UA075.002.016.00032 (Box 16)
  - Howell, Richard, Jr., 1980; UA075.002.016.00033 (Box 16)
  - Howland, John S II, 1979; UA075.002.016.00034 (Box 16)
  - Hoye, Davis, 1975; UA075.002.016.00035 (Box 16)
  - Hoye, Kathleen (Sullivan), 1980; UA075.002.016.00036 (Box 16)
  - Hoye, Sara Ann, 1980; UA075.002.016.00037 (Box 16)
  - Hsia, Henry, 1984; UA075.002.016.00038 (Box 16)
  - Hsu, Charlene Chia-Ling (Winges), 1976; UA075.002.016.00039 (Box 16)
  - Huang, John, 1982; UA075.002.016.00040 (Box 16)
  - Hubbard, Marcia L., 1977; UA075.002.016.00041 (Box 16)
  - Hudson, Fadrienne (see Sessions), 1985; UA075.002.016.00042 (Box 16)
  - Hudson, James I II, 1979; UA075.002.016.00043 (Box 16)
  - Hudson, Margo Silbar, 1979; UA075.002.016.00044 (Box 16)
  - Hummel, William P., 1979; UA075.002.016.00045 (Box 16)
  - Humphries, Thomas Joel, 1970; UA075.002.016.00046 (Box 16)
  - Hunt, Lillian, 1982; UA075.002.016.00047 (Box 16)
  - Hunt, Sean, 1980; UA075.002.016.00048 (Box 16)
  - Hunter, Elsie Marie, 1978; UA075.002.016.00049 (Box 16)
  - Hurwitz, Edward Frank, 1975; UA075.002.016.00050 (Box 16)
  - Hyatt, Jr., John Robert, 1978; UA075.002.016.00051 (Box 16)
  - Hymanson, Bruce H., 1977; UA075.002.016.00052 (Box 16)
  - Ingram, Jr., Irving E., 1977; UA075.002.016.00053 (Box 16)
  - Inouye, Alice Masami, 1978; UA075.002.016.00054 (Box 16)
  - Irons, David, 1980; UA075.002.016.00055 (Box 16)
  - Iuster, Raluca, 1983; UA075.002.016.00056 (Box 16)
  - Jackson, Michael V., 1978; UA075.002.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - Jackson, Ralph Kiner, 1975; UA075.002.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Jacoby, Wendy Shaw, 1981; UA075.002.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Jaffe, Robert M., 1978; UA075.002.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - James, Deanna Rosemond, 1983; UA075.002.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - James, Leonard, 1984; UA075.002.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - Jankelson, Julie, 1983; UA075.002.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - Jaro, Marlene F, 1979; UA075.002.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - Jennings, Anne, 1980; UA075.002.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - Jennings, L. Candace, 1983; UA075.002.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - Johnson, David Scott, 1965; UA075.002.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Larry Hugh, 1975; UA075.002.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - Johson, Michael, 1983; UA075.002.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Molly, 1983; UA075.002.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Peter Bedros, 1981; UA075.002.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Richard, 1980; UA075.002.017.00016 (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Shirley A., 1977; UA075.002.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - Jones, Clement Kevin, 1982; UA075.002.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - Jones, Dawna, 1984; UA075.002.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - Jones, Helena, 1981; UA075.002.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - Jones, Ronald A., 1980; UA075.002.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - Joslin, Allen D., 1977; UA075.002.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - Joyce, Daniel, 1983; UA075.002.017.00023 (Box 17)
  - Joyce, Ellen, 1975; UA075.002.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - Jueppner, Harald, 1981; UA075.002.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - Kahn, Katherine, 1976; UA075.002.017.00026 (Box 17)
  - Kalayjian, Robert, 1982; UA075.002.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - Kallayee, Dalia, 1974; UA075.002.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - Kalliel, John, 1982; UA075.002.017.00029 (Box 17)
  - Kaminsky, John, 1983; UA075.002.017.00030 (Box 17)
  - Kamoski, Liudomir Edward, 1961; UA075.002.017.00031 (Box 17)
  - Kane, Anne, 1984; UA075.002.017.00032 (Box 17)
  - Kane, Barbara J., 1982; UA075.002.017.00033 (Box 17)
  - Kangos, James Alexis, 1977; UA075.002.017.00034 (Box 17)
  - Kantrowitz, Micki, 1983; UA075.002.017.00035 (Box 17)
  - Kaplan, Charles, 1984; UA075.002.017.00036 (Box 17)
  - Kaplan, Kennell, 1985; UA075.002.017.00037 (Box 17)
  - Kaplan, Paul David, 1975; UA075.002.017.00038 (Box 17)
  - Karchere, Martha G., 1977; UA075.002.017.00039 (Box 17)
  - Karlson, Lynne, 1981; UA075.002.017.00040 (Box 17)
  - Kasparian, Glenn Derr, 1975; UA075.002.017.00041 (Box 17)
  - Kass, Frederic, 1984; UA075.002.017.00042 (Box 17)
  - Kasser, James R., 1976; UA075.002.017.00043 (Box 17)
  - Kasuba, Paul, 1984; UA075.002.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Katz, David S., 1977; UA075.002.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - Katz, Howard Michael, 1974; UA075.002.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - Katz, Stuart Eric, 1976; UA075.002.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - Katz, Neil T, 1981; UA075.002.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - Kaufman, Ellen G., 1978; UA075.002.018.00006 (Box 18)
  - Kaufman, Jefferey G., 1975; UA075.002.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - Kaufman, Robert Joseph, Jr., 1975; UA075.002.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - Kavanah, Maureen Teresa, 1975; UA075.002.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - Kaye, Mitchell D., 1981; UA075.002.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - Kazanjian, Powel H. Jr., 1979; UA075.002.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - Kazer, Ralph R., 1979; UA075.002.018.00012 (Box 18)
  - Kearney, Thomas Anthony, 1975; UA075.002.018.00013 (Box 18)
  - Kearns, Paul Thomas, 1975; UA075.002.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - Keating, Thomas, 1983; UA075.002.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - Keene, Maura Ellen (Atkins), 1981; UA075.002.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - Kelfer, Howard Michael, 1976; UA075.002.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - Kelleher, Raymond Joseph Jr., 1965; UA075.002.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - Keller, Gary A., 1981; UA075.002.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - Kelley, William Joseph, 1976; UA075.002.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - Kelley, Amalia (Choman), 1979; UA075.002.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - Kelley, Barbara A., 1977; UA075.002.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - Kelly, Benson, 1983; UA075.002.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - Kelly, Diane, 1978; UA075.002.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - Kelly, John Joseph, 1977; UA075.002.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - Kelly, Sara, 1985; UA075.002.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - Kendall, Cheryl Jones, 1981; UA075.002.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - Kennedy, Bruce Shawn, 1981; UA075.002.018.00028 (Box 18)
  - Kennedy, Maura, 1984; UA075.002.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - Kerlinsky, Daniel, 1978; UA075.002.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - Kern, Donald C., 1977; UA075.002.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - Keroak, Brian, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.002.018.00032 (Box 18)
  - Kershaw, Paul R., 1981; UA075.002.018.00033 (Box 18)
  - Kiger, Peter N., 1977; UA075.002.018.00034 (Box 18)
  - Kile, Debra Hope (NFE Chaimowitz), 1982; UA075.002.018.00035 (Box 18)
  - Kile, Paul Edward, 1982; UA075.002.018.00036 (Box 18)
  - Killen, Kevin, 1983; UA075.002.018.00037 (Box 18)
  - Killen, John Young Jr., 1975; UA075.002.018.00038 (Box 18)
  - Kim, Hyo J., 1977; UA075.002.018.00039 (Box 18)
  - Kim, Myung Ja (Jean), 1981; UA075.002.018.00040 (Box 18)
  - Kinder, Richard A., 1981; UA075.002.018.00041 (Box 18)
  - Kinderlehrer, Daniel Abram, 1975; UA075.002.018.00042 (Box 18)
  - Kindig, Ronald, 1983; UA075.002.018.00043 (Box 18)
  - King, Judith A., 1980; UA075.002.018.00044 (Box 18)
  - Kinlaw, William B., 1977; UA075.002.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Kipersztok, Simon, 1983; UA075.002.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - Kirschbaum, Lisa Sue, 1984; UA075.002.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Klainer, Paul, 1980; UA075.002.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - Klein, Harvey, 1980; UA075.002.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - Klein, Karen Ellen, 1976; UA075.002.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Kleinbaum, Jerry I., 1976; UA075.002.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Klementowicz, Peter T., 1978; UA075.002.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Kline, Thomas Jefferson, 1985; UA075.002.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - Klink, Arlene, 1982; UA075.002.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Klinker, Mark, 1985; UA075.002.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Klucznik, Richard, 1983; UA075.002.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - Kneeland, Jr., John Fobb, 1975; UA075.002.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - Kneeland, Michael D., 1980; UA075.002.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - Knowlton, Stephen Dana, 1978; UA075.002.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Kobzik, Lester, 1979; UA075.002.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - Koch, Paul S., 1977; UA075.002.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - Koch, Sandra, UA075.002.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - Koehler, Karl Alexander, 1973; UA075.002.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - Koehler, Richard, 1982; UA075.002.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - Konefal, Jr. Stanley Henry, 1975; UA075.002.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - Koplan, Jefferey Powell, 1970; UA075.002.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - Korff, Jefferey Michael, 1975; UA075.002.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - Korkosz, Tanya J., 1977; UA075.002.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - Kornberg, Mark, 1977; UA075.002.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - Kosten, David, 1984; UA075.002.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - Kowal, Keith, 1983; UA075.002.019.00027 (Box 19)
  - Kowalski, Henryk M., 1981; UA075.002.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - Kraft, Philip B., 1976; UA075.002.019.00029 (Box 19)
  - Kraftowitz, Robert, 1978; UA075.002.019.00030 (Box 19)
  - Krieger, David Joshua, 1975; UA075.002.019.00031 (Box 19)
  - Krinsky, J. Erwin, 1977; UA075.002.019.00032 (Box 19)
  - Krizan, Kelly J., 1978; UA075.002.019.00033 (Box 19)
  - Kunkel, Mark Jay, 1975; UA075.002.019.00034 (Box 19)
  - Kuo, Irving, 1980; UA075.002.019.00035 (Box 19)
  - Kuperman, Joseph, 1975; UA075.002.019.00036 (Box 19)
  - Kuppersmith, Stephen J., 1977; UA075.002.019.00037 (Box 19)
  - Kurlansky, Paul, 1980; UA075.002.019.00038 (Box 19)
  - Kurlantzick, Robert, 1982; UA075.002.019.00039 (Box 19)
  - Kushman, Brian Scott, 1976; UA075.002.019.00040 (Box 19)
  - Kusick, Daniel, 1985; UA075.002.019.00041 (Box 19)
  - Kutnick, Richard T., 1976; UA075.002.019.00042 (Box 19)
  - Kwan, Eddie S.K., 1977; UA075.002.019.00043 (Box 19)
  - Melvin, Terry, 1984; UA075.002.024.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 1)
    75 years from date of creation.
  - Memoli, Vincent Alfred, 1976; UA075.002.024.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Mendel, Jeffrey B., 1977; UA075.002.024.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Mendel, Joyce, 1978; UA075.002.024.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Mendiguren, Ignacio, 1980 -- 1984; UA075.002.024.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Mendis, Roger, 1984; UA075.002.024.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Mesrobian, Alexander Leon, 1982; UA075.002.024.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Messier, Mark, 1982; UA075.002.024.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Meyer, Donald, 1975; UA075.002.024.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Meyers, Julie, 1978 -- 1983; UA075.002.024.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Mezer, Howard, C., 1977; UA075.002.024.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Miceli, Robert Gerard, 1976; UA075.002.024.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Michaelson, Wendy S., 1979; UA075.002.024.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Michaud, Judith Slattery, 1970 -- 1971; UA075.002.024.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Michaud, Vincent, 1982; UA075.002.024.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Miesfeldt, Susan, 1984; UA075.002.024.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Mikulis, David J., 1976 -- 1981; UA075.002.024.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Miler, Veronica, 1981; UA075.002.024.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Miller, Denise, 1983; UA075.002.024.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Miller, Gary, 1983; UA075.002.024.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Miller, Hugh, 1985; UA075.002.024.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Miller Jr., E. Huxley, 1977; UA075.002.024.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Miller, Karin, 1982; UA075.002.024.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Miller, Karen Leslie, 1976; UA075.002.024.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Miller, Kenneth, 1977 -- 1982; UA075.002.024.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Miller, Michael C., 1974 -- 1978; UA075.002.024.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Miller, William, 1980; UA075.002.024.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Milliken Jr., John (Jeff) F., 1974 -- 1980; UA075.002.024.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Mills, Charles, 1979; UA075.002.024.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Minaker, Burt, 1976 -- 1980; UA075.002.024.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Miniter, Paul, 1983; UA075.002.024.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Mintz, Martin Paul, 1962 -- 1963; UA075.002.024.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Mischel, Matthew, 1984; UA075.002.024.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Misslbeck, James Gareth, 1976 -- 1982; UA075.002.024.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Mizel, Mark S., 1977; UA075.002.024.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Model, Ellyn H, 1979; UA075.002.024.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Moffitt, Elizabeth, 1983; UA075.002.024.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Moller, David R., 1979; UA075.002.024.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Molloy, Philip J., 1981; UA075.002.024.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Monahan, William Robert, 1963 -- 1965; UA075.002.024.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Monroy, Peter A., 1976; UA075.002.024.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Monteiro, Andrew Robert, 1982; UA075.002.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - Montminy, Marc, 1984; UA075.002.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - Moore, Stephen, 1983; UA075.002.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - Moran, Sean, 1984; UA075.002.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - Moran, Thomas Joseph, 1985; UA075.002.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - Morin, David, 1984; UA075.002.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - Morin, John B., 1978; UA075.002.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - Morrill, Diane J. (formerly Kelly, Diane), 1978; UA075.002.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - Morris, Kathleen, 1985; UA075.002.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - Morrison, Robert C., 1978; UA075.002.025.00010 (Box 25)
  - Morse, James, 1983; UA075.002.025.00011 (Box 25)
  - Moskowitz, Steven, 1984; UA075.002.025.00012 (Box 25)
  - Moss, Debra L., 1980; UA075.002.025.00013 (Box 25)
  - Motta, Mario E., 1978; UA075.002.025.00014 (Box 25)
  - Moulton, Paul, 1984; UA075.002.025.00015 (Box 25)
  - Moussa, Pierre, 1986; UA075.002.025.00016 (Box 25)
  - Moy, Janet A., 1979; UA075.002.025.00017 (Box 25)
  - Moy, Wing-AR (Patrick), 1977; UA075.002.025.00018 (Box 25)
  - Mozzicato, Patricia, 1985; UA075.002.025.00019 (Box 25)
  - Mufson, Michael Jon, 1976; UA075.002.025.00020 (Box 25)
  - Mughelli, Michael Olumide, 1980; UA075.002.025.00021 (Box 25)
  - Mullen, Mark, 1980; UA075.002.025.00022 (Box 25)
  - Mullan, Sara Ann Hoye (Formerly Hoye, Sara), 1980; UA075.002.025.00023 (Box 25)
  - Mullarkey, Cathleen, 1984; UA075.002.025.00024 (Box 25)
  - Mulligan, Michael, 1980; UA075.002.025.00025 (Box 25)
  - Mulroy, John, 1984; UA075.002.025.00026 (Box 25)
  - Mulroy, Richard D., Jr., 1981; UA075.002.025.00027 (Box 25)
  - Mulvey, Therese, 1985; UA075.002.025.00028 (Box 25)
  - Munson, Dianne, 1975; UA075.002.025.00029 (Box 25)
  - Murphy, K., 1980; UA075.002.025.00030 (Box 25)
  - Murphy, Michael Bruce, 1974; UA075.002.025.00031 (Box 25)
  - Murphy, Timothy F., 1976; UA075.002.025.00032 (Box 25)
  - Murphy, William C., Jr., 1981; UA075.002.025.00033 (Box 25)
  - Murray, Jefferey C., 1978; UA075.002.025.00034 (Box 25)
  - Murrell, Walter J., 1981; UA075.002.025.00035 (Box 25)
  - Murzic, William, 1984; UA075.002.025.00036 (Box 25)
  - Musliner, Jacqueline Olds (formerly Jacqueline Olds), 1971; UA075.002.025.00037 (Box 25)
  - Nabrit-Stephens, Barbara Anne, UA075.002.025.00038 (Box 25)
  - Nadeau, Steven A., 1981; UA075.002.025.00039 (Box 25)
  - Nagi, Constance, 1977; UA075.002.025.00040 (Box 25)
  - Nahigyan, Drew, 1984; UA075.002.025.00041 (Box 25)
  - Najjar, Jennifer, 1977; UA075.002.025.00042 (Box 25)
  - Napier, Thomas, 1985; UA075.002.025.00043 (Box 25)
  - Nash, Stephen, 1983; UA075.002.025.00044 (Box 25)
  - Nasif, Ronald J., 1979; UA075.002.025.00045 (Box 25)
  - Naturman, Roy, 1983; UA075.002.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - Negron, Cynthia, 1985; UA075.002.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - Nehme, Ann Marie, 1983; UA075.002.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - Neifeld, Gary, 1981; UA075.002.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - Neptune, David E., 1978; UA075.002.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - Neptune, Doreen A., 1979; UA075.002.026.00006 (Box 26)
  - Nesin, Noah, 1983; UA075.002.026.00007 (Box 26)
  - Nesto, Richard William, 1976; UA075.002.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - Neustein, Paulk, 1979; UA075.002.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - Newman, Steven B., 1977; UA075.002.026.00010 (Box 26)
  - Newton, Elizabeth Hsu, 1981; UA075.002.026.00011 (Box 26)
  - NG, Richard, 1984; UA075.002.026.00012 (Box 26)
  - Nicholson, Romero, 1984; UA075.002.026.00013 (Box 26)
  - Nielsen, James Leroy, 1975; UA075.002.026.00014 (Box 26)
  - Nielsen, Lars, 1982; UA075.002.026.00015 (Box 26)
  - Noel, Ruth E., 1978; UA075.002.026.00016 (Box 26)
  - Nolan, Christopher, 1977; UA075.002.026.00017 (Box 26)
  - Noonan, Susan, 1980; UA075.002.026.00018 (Box 26)
  - Nordberg, Joanne, 1983; UA075.002.026.00019 (Box 26)
  - Nowell, Martha A., 1978; UA075.002.026.00020 (Box 26)
  - Nowicki, Philip T., 1978; UA075.002.026.00021 (Box 26)
  - Nsien, Ephraim, 1983; UA075.002.026.00022 (Box 26)
  - O'Brien, Jane E., 1979; UA075.002.026.00023 (Box 26)
  - Ocasio, Jr., Heriberto, 1978; UA075.002.026.00024 (Box 26)
  - O'Connell, Kathleen M., 1981; UA075.002.026.00025 (Box 26)
  - O'Connor, Joseph Robert, 1975; UA075.002.026.00026 (Box 26)
  - O'Grady, Glennon, 1985; UA075.002.026.00027 (Box 26)
  - O'Leary, Gloria, 1983; UA075.002.026.00028 (Box 26)
  - Olekowiscz, Leslie, 1982; UA075.002.026.00029 (Box 26)
  - Oliver, Donald Everett, 1975; UA075.002.026.00030 (Box 26)
  - On, Roger C., 1978; UA075.002.026.00031 (Box 26)
  - O'Neil, Kathleen M., 1978; UA075.002.026.00032 (Box 26)
  - O'Neill, William C IV, 1979; UA075.002.026.00033 (Box 26)
  - Ono, Rodney, 1980; UA075.002.026.00034 (Box 26)
  - Orlando, Ralph P., 1978; UA075.002.026.00035 (Box 26)
  - Ortiz, Louise, 1981; UA075.002.026.00036 (Box 26)
  - Osnoss, Kenneth Lawrence, 1975; UA075.002.026.00037 (Box 26)
  - Ossoff, Robert H., 1975; UA075.002.026.00038 (Box 26)
  - Ostrowski, Mary, 1980; UA075.002.026.00039 (Box 26)
  - Oullette, Patricia, 1983; UA075.002.026.00040 (Box 26)
  - Overby, (Michael) Chris, 1979; UA075.002.026.00041 (Box 26)
  - Owen, William F., Jr., 1980; UA075.002.026.00042 (Box 26)
  - Palmero, Francis Xavier, 1979; UA075.002.026.00043 (Box 26)
  - Paley, Robert Hunter, 1975; UA075.002.026.00044 (Box 26)
  - Palmer, Edwin L., 1978; UA075.002.026.00045 (Box 26)
  - Palmer, Millicent L., 1980; UA075.002.026.00046 (Box 26)
  - Pals, Steven, 1985; UA075.002.026.00047 (Box 26)
  - Pancho, Linda, 1982; UA075.002.026.00048 (Box 26)
  - Papadeas, Vicki, 1980; UA075.002.026.00049 (Box 26)
  - Parrish, Richard M., 1975; UA075.002.027.00001 (Box 27)
  - Pathroff, Robert Alan, 1982; UA075.002.027.00002 (Box 27)
  - Patten, Deborah L., 1981; UA075.002.027.00003 (Box 27)
  - Patten, Jennifer, 1982; UA075.002.027.00004 (Box 27)
  - Patterson, James Lewis, 1977; UA075.002.027.00005 (Box 27)
  - Pauker, Kenneth Yurdin, 1976; UA075.002.027.00006 (Box 27)
  - Paul, Maureen, 1979; UA075.002.027.00007 (Box 27)
  - Paull, Daniel, 1978; UA075.002.027.00008 (Box 27)
  - Payne, Jr. Robert Dawson, 1976; UA075.002.027.00009 (Box 27)
  - Pearlmutter, Mark, 1984; UA075.002.027.00010 (Box 27)
  - Pearson, Gail D., 1979; UA075.002.027.00011 (Box 27)
  - Peaslee, Steven, 1984; UA075.002.027.00012 (Box 27)
  - Pelletier, Maureen, 1984; UA075.002.027.00013 (Box 27)
  - Pennacchio, Joseph L., 1976; UA075.002.027.00014 (Box 27)
  - Peoples, Ulysses Simpson Grant, 1976; UA075.002.027.00015 (Box 27)
  - Pepper, Gary Mark, 1976; UA075.002.027.00016 (Box 27)
  - Perkins, Paul Franklin III, 1975; UA075.002.027.00017 (Box 27)
  - Perlo, David, 1975; UA075.002.027.00018 (Box 27)
  - Perlo, Laura, 1985; UA075.002.027.00019 (Box 27)
  - Permesly, Lester Scott, 1971; UA075.002.027.00020 (Box 27)
  - Perr, Norman, 1979; UA075.002.027.00021 (Box 27)
  - Perrine, Susan P., 1976; UA075.002.027.00022 (Box 27)
  - Perron, Jonathan James, 1974; UA075.002.027.00023 (Box 27)
  - Perry, Linda, 1985; UA075.002.027.00024 (Box 27)
  - Perry, Loring, 1987; UA075.002.027.00025 (Box 27)
  - Petersen, Kathleen Bourassa, 1983; UA075.002.027.00026 (Box 27)
  - Petersen, Kevin, 1981; UA075.002.027.00027 (Box 27)
  - Peterson, Christine Marie, 1976; UA075.002.027.00028 (Box 27)
  - Peterson, David B., 1981; UA075.002.027.00029 (Box 27)
  - Peterson, Gregory Scott, 1982; UA075.002.027.00030 (Box 27)
  - Peterson, Ross King, 1973; UA075.002.027.00031 (Box 27)
  - Peterson, Thomas Russell, 1976; UA075.002.027.00032 (Box 27)
  - Petrillo, Enrico, 1980; UA075.002.027.00033 (Box 27)
  - Phillips, Cathy A., 1979; UA075.002.027.00034 (Box 27)
  - Phillips, David, 1983; UA075.002.027.00035 (Box 27)